你看  那个就是边锋
<i>Okay, so that's the tight end,</i>
他旁边的那个是散锋
And the guy next to him is called the split end.
散锋
Split end?
注：Split end也有头发分叉的意思
如果用飘柔洗头后  他们管他叫什么啊
What do they call him after he shampoos and conditions?
算了  还是不看橄榄球了
Yeah, let's not watch football.
嘿  咱们应该商量下舞会的事情
Hey, we should talk about prom.
我就在想  如果你六点来
So I was thinking, if you show up by 6:00,
我们就可以照点照片
Then we can do some pictures.
-如果我们六点半走  -泰迪  别急  我还没邀请你去舞会呢
-Then if we left by 6:30... -Teddy, hold on. I haven't even asked you yet.
是吗  我只是假设了下  毕竟咱俩是恋人关系
Well, I just assumed. I mean, we're boyfriend and girlfriend.
是啊  我知道  但我觉得还是应该邀请你一下
Yeah, I know, but I still think I should ask you.
邀请的流程不能略过
It's kind of how it's done.
好吧  来吧  邀请我
Fine, go ahead, ask me.
泰迪  你愿意和我一起去舞会吗
Teddy, would you like to go to the prom with me?
-不  -等等  你说啥
-No. -Wait. What?
首先你把邀请这件事弄得小题大做
Well, first you make a whole big deal out of the invitation,
然后你又随口一问
Then you just blurt it out?
浪漫在哪  你的诚心在哪
Where's the romance, the heart?
那我应该重头再来一遍吗
Maybe I should start over.
是的  我感觉有这个必要
Yeah, I think that would be best.
-泰迪  你愿意  -不  不  不  不
-Teddy, would you like to go to the... -No, no, no, no.
门外边  从那里开始
Go outside. Start over there.
去啊  去啊
Go on, go on.
如果要做  就要做对
If we're gonna do this, do it right.
我来开门
I'll get it.
泰迪·邓肯
Teddy Duncan,
能否赏个脸
would you do me the honor
准许我陪同你去参加舞会吗
of allowing me to escort you to the prom?
噢  眼泪都出来了  我的天啊
Oh, you're tearing up. Oh, my gosh.
我当然愿意和你一起去了  宝贝
Of course I'll go with you, baby.
-被花刺扎到手了  是吧  -恩  恩
-Got stuck by a thorn, didn't you? -Uh-huh.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第四集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E04  Dress Mess
你俩干啥呢
What are you guys doing?
看一下我的年鉴  试着找个舞伴
I'm looking through my yearbook, trying to find a prom date.
是啊  我在边上看是因为等我到高中后
Yeah, and I'm watching him so I can see what mistakes
可以避免同样的悲剧发生在我身上
to avoid when I'm in High School.
PJ  舞会就在这周六
P.J., prom's this Saturday.
你最好抓紧了
You might wanna hurry up.
噢  没关系  我看过他的成绩单
Oh, it's okay. I've seen his report card.
他很可能会有两场以上的毕业舞会
He'll probably have two more senior proms.
嘿  你知道辛西娅·马尔考斯基吗
Hey, what do you know about Cynthia Markowski?
她以前是天才班的  提前毕业了
She was in the gifted program and graduated early.
白痴的天才
Stupid smart people.
嘿  罗宾·罗杰斯怎么样
Hey, what about Robin Rogers?
-看起来挺可爱的  -那是男的
-She's pretty cute. -That's a guy.
你去年的舞伴是谁
Who was your date last year?
我组团去的
I went with a group.
现在我们称呼艾米特为“团”吗
So now we're calling Emmett a group?
天无绝人之路  总会有适合我的
There's gotta be somebody out there for me.
只是希望能及时现身
I just Hope I find her in time.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
你的匹萨
Here's your pizza.
谢谢
Thanks.
如果走狗屎运的话
With any luck,
PJ可能找到舞伴了
P.J. May have just found his prom date.
我能问件事吗
Can I ask you something?
可以  随便问
Sure, anything.
你们卖奇奇怪怪面包吗
Do you guys have any wacky bread?
是啊  估计光是狗屎运还不够
Yeah, it's gonna take a little more than luck.
你出马吧
Get over there.
好了  看起来不错  孩子的情况很好
Well, things look good. The baby's doing great,
但是我有点担心体重问题
but I'm a little concerned about the weight gain.
我觉着体重没涨那么多吧
I really haven't gained that much.
不  我说的是他
No, I mean him.
开玩笑的  我们就喜欢开玩笑  是吧  玛西亚
Just kidding. We like to have fun here, right, Marcia?
想要一段你们的超声波影像吗
So would you like a DVD of your ultrasound?
-想  -不想
-Yes. -No.
我以为我们不急于知道是男孩还是女孩
I thought we agreed we wanted to wait to find out if it's a boy or a girl.
不是想要个惊喜吗
We want to be surprised.
我不想要惊喜  我想要知道
I don't like surprises. I want to know.
但是作为婴儿的母体
And the person carrying the baby
认为不知道为妙
Thinks it's better not to know.
我们喜欢惊喜
We'd like to be surprised.
请把这个放进邓肯资料里
Put this in the Duncan file, please.
没关心的
That's okay.
我们不用知道
We don't need to know.
只要我们的宝宝是健康的  对吧  医生
As long as our baby boy is healthy, right, doc?
我的意思是  重要的是我们的宝贝闺女
I mean, the main thing is that our baby girl
是健康的  对吧  医生
is doing great, right, doc?
亲爱的  老鲍  这位又不傻
Bob, honey, the man's not an idiot.
人家有医学学位  对吧  医生
He has a medical degree. Right, doc?
谢了
Thanks.
这第一次约会真的肯开心
That was a really fun first date.
泰勒  以我的经验来看
Taylor, in my experience,
你在迷你高尔夫球上很有天赋
you can never go wrong with mini golf.
PJ  我知道咱俩刚刚相识
P.J., I know we just met,
但我能问你个问题吗
but can I ask you something?
好的  但是问题别太难  因为我不想破坏这次约会
Okay, but nothing too hard, 'cause this date's going really well.
我的毕业舞会是在这周六
My senior prom is this Saturday,
我在想你是不是能和我一起去
and I was wondering if you would like to go with me.
-呃  噢  -问题太难了吗
-Uh-oh. -Too hard?
不  不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no, no.
只是我的毕业舞会也是在周六
It's just my senior prom is also this Saturday.
我很是兴奋
I was really excited about it,
本打算想邀请你
and I was gonna ask you.
噢
Oh.
但是你先提出了邀请  那我就同意吧
But you asked me first, so yes.
噢  跟你说一下  我也会同意的
Oh, and just so you know, I would have said yes.
好的
Yes!
-那就不见不散了  -没问题
-Then it's a date? -Absolutely.
等等  我们去谁的毕业舞会呢
Wait, whose prom are we going to?
应该是我的吧
Mine, I think.
-耶  耶  -耶
-Yeah, yeah. -Yeah.
在宝宝出生后
And after the baby's born,
妈咪和爹地就会把他从医院接回来
mommy and daddy will bring it home from the hospital.
那他们什么时候再把他接走呢
But when do they take it back?
查莉  他们不会再把宝宝接走了
Charlie, they don't take the babies back.
我懂的  曾经我也想让盖比回去
I know. I tried with Gabe.
泰迪  你在这里啊
Teddy, there you are.
嘿  听着  我问一下  你选好舞会的裙子了吗
Hey, listen, I was wondering if you've picked out a prom dress yet.
没有  我应该去买一条
No, I really need to go shopping.
或者不用了
Or not.
老妈  我需要买条裙子
Mom, I need to buy a dress.
我不能随便从衣柜里挑一件穿上
I can't just wear something from my closet.
也许不在你的衣柜里挑
Maybe not <i>your</i> closet.
感觉情况不妙
I don't like where this is going.
让我给你讲个故事
Let me tell you a story
在当时就是个悲剧啊
that seemed tragic at the time,
但如今终于要画上完美的句点了
but is now finally gonna have a happy ending.
情况真的很不妙啊
I really don't like where this is going.
1988的那一年
The year was 1988,
青春美丽的艾米·布兰肯琥珀
and a young and beautiful Amy blankenhooper
走在前往舞会的路上  和她的第三选择  鲍勃·邓肯
was on her way to the prom with her third choice Bob Duncan.
但是  情况发展得和艾米所计划的不一样
But alas, all would not turn out as Amy had planned.
得知这个故事要讲上一阵子
Knowing this story would go on for a while,
泰迪坐下了
Teddy sat down.
鲍勃·迪斗鲍克  艾米的首选
Bob Diddlebock, Amy's first choice,
带着他的舞伴去吃牛排
took his date out for steak.
鲍勃·邓肯拿着优惠券去吃臭虾
Bob Duncan had a coupon for the shrimp Bucket.
总之  那是一个撑破肚皮的夜晚
Anyway, it was an all-you-can-eat night,
艾米尝试跟上鲍勃的节奏
and Amy tried to keep up with Bob,
那是她的第二个错误
which was her second mistake.
一个使她那条价值不菲的裙子
A mistake that her beautiful prom dress
万劫不复的错误
would pay for dearly.
你想说什么
So what are you saying...
你吐在舞会礼服上了吗
Did you puke on your prom dress?
那个  在1988年  我们称之为“呕”
Well, in 1988, we called it "hurling."
如今这个悲剧的故事终于要有个美好的结局了
Now this sad little story is finally gonna have a happy ending.
泰迪  明白吗
Teddy, don't you see?
我保留这条裙子多年
I saved that prom dress all these years
就是为了日后能让你穿上
so that you could wear it to your prom.
我去拿
I'll go get it.
老妈  你真的不用
Mom, you really don't have to...
闪瞎你的眼
Ba-bam!
泰迪  当这条裙子出现在舞会上时
Teddy, when this dress goes to the prom,
就好像是我在舞会上
it'll almost be like I finally get to go to the prom.
要真是你就好了
I wish it were you.
对了  查莉
And, Charlie,
也许你也可以穿这条裙子去舞会
maybe you can wear this to your prom, too.
算了  谢谢  妈咪
No, thank you, mommy.
好吧  你干啥呢  老爸
Okay. Whatcha doing, dad?
噢  只是想想咱家的新成员
Oh, just thinking about the new baby.
好吧  我一般都喜欢去楼上思考问题
Yeah, I like to do my thinking upstairs,
就是避免妨碍有人想来楼下
just in case someone wants to come down here,
玩会电子游戏什么的
play some video games or something.
知道吗  我只想知道
You know, all I want to know
是男孩还是女孩
is if it's gonna be a boy or a girl.
但是你妈老想要个惊喜
But your mother wants to be surprised.
干嘛不自己去问问然后瞒着老妈
Why don't you find out and then not tell mom?
你的大脑你做主
You have a brain of your own, right?
当然了
Of course I do.
只是你老妈的大脑不喜欢
It's just that your mother's brain doesn't like it
我的大脑自己做主
when my brain goes off on its own.
老爸  你不能当老妈的提线木偶
Dad, you can't just do whatever mom tells you to do.
你要为你自己反抗
You have to stand up for yourself.
知道吗  你给医生打电话  你有权利知道一切
You know, you have to call the doctor and you have to demand to know.
-你还别说  你真说对了  -对了
-You know what? You're right. -Right?
-我是说  我是孩子他爹  -没错  你是
-I mean, I am the baby's father. -Yes, you are.
是的  我有权利知道
Yes, I do have some rights.
您好  玛西亚  我是鲍勃·邓肯
<i>Hello.</i> <i>Marcia, Bob Duncan.</i>
我不想打扰到医生  我只是想让你
I don't wanna bother the doctor. I was just... could you...
帮帮忙  你能瞄一眼档案吗
For me, could you just take a little look-see in our file
告诉我是男孩还是女孩
and just tell me if we're gonna have a boy or a girl?
好的  当然
Okay, sure.
快说  她说什么了
All right, what did she say?
让我别挂  她要向你老妈打电话汇报
Would I please hold while she calls your mother?
成了  接受吧  老爸
Well, face it, dad.
你的大脑比不过老妈的
Your brain's no match for mom's.
但是算你走运  我有个计划
But lucky for you, I have a plan.
邪恶的计划吗
Is it an evil plan?
不  不  不
No, no, no.
是个救助穷人的计划
It's a plan that helps the poor.
当然了  当然是个邪恶的计划
Of course, it's an evil plan.
我也不知道了
I don't know.
噢  别这样  你知道自己想这样的
Oh, come on. You know you want to do it.
难道这不是你第一个来找我的原因吗
Isn't that why you came to me in the first place?
好吧
Yeah.
-哇  你好漂亮啊  -你也是
-Wow! You look great. -So do you.
-进来吧  -好的
-Come on in. -Okay.
我们到了
Here we are.
-到哪了  -舞会啊
-What is this? -It's the prom.
你家里的舞会
Your prom is here in your house?
是啊  我在家上学
Yeah, I'm homeschooled.
这就是舞会的全部了吗
So this is the whole prom?
只有你和我
Just you and me
和一些老太太
and some old lady?
噢  那是我奶奶
Oh, that's my grandma.
她也同样是DJ
She's also the dj.
她为什么戴着墨西哥草帽
Why's she wearing a sombrero?
因为舞会的主题是
Because the theme of the prom
“国境之南”
is "south of the border."
噢  好吧  那就合理了
Oh, okay, that makes sense.
刚才有那么一刻  我感觉挺奇怪的
For a second there, I thought it was weird.
好啊  孩子们
<i>Hola,</i> kids!
聚会开始吧  亲们
Let the fiesta begin. <i>Ole!</i>
PJ  这是我妈妈
P.J., this is my mom.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
也是我的生物老师  历史老师
And my biology teacher and my history teacher
-数学老师  -好了  照相吧
-and my math teacher. -All right, picture time.
笑一笑  照片会放在年鉴上
Now smile. It's for the yearbook.
我知道这有点不同寻常
I know this is a little unusual.
也许我应该早点告诉你我在家上学
I guess I should have told you I was homeschooled.
总比不知道强
But it had been good information to have
噢  抱歉
Oh, excuse me.
至少事情不能再怪异了
Well, at least it's not getting any weirder.
嗨  咿
Hi... yee!
觉着咋样
So what do you think?
我  呃
I, uh...
呃
Uh...
算了  放松  我在灌木丛里藏了另一套礼服
No, relax, I've got a different dress hidden in the bushes.
好吧  那你干嘛穿着这件
Well, then why are you wearing that one?
泰迪  你简直美极了
Teddy, you almost look as beautiful
和我穿起来一样美
in that dress as I did.
当我没问
Never mind.
好了  照相了
Okay, picture time.
好了  你往后  别压到花边
Okay, back it up. You're crushing the ruffles.
不错
Good one.
好了  看这里  看这里
Okay, over here. Over here.
看这里  收下巴  斯宾塞
Over here. Chin down, Spencer.
好了  老妈  别照了  我们该走了
Okay, mom, come on, we have to go.
好吧  玩的开心  噢  等等  等等
Okay, have fun. Oh, wait! Wait.
我差点忘了  我有个惊喜
I almost forgot. I have a surprise.
配套的帽子
The matching hat!
噢
Oh!
噢  现在我的头也难逃此劫
Oh, now my head can be as lucky as the rest of me.
-嘿  打扰一下  你是卡普医生吗  -是的
-Hey, excuse me, are you Dr. Karp? -Yes.
嗨  我是盖比·邓肯
Hi, I'm Gabe Duncan.
-噢  -幸会
-Oh! -Nice to meet you.
这是查莉
And this is Charlie.
说实话  我们来这里是因为她对于
You know, we're here because she's having a hard time
未来家里的新成员有些疑问
with the new baby thing.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie,
这位可以为你解除心中所有的疑问
here's the man who can make you happy again.
和他谈谈
Talk to him.
我要有个弟弟还是妹妹
Will I have a little sister or little brother?
噢  你听到了吗
Awww, did you hear that?
她说的“涕涕还是咩咩”多可爱啊
She said, "a wittle sisto or wittle brudder."
谁能拒绝啊
Who can say no to that?
我能
I could.
如果未经你的父母同意就告诉你  那我还算什么医生
What kind of doctor would I be if I told you without your parents' permission?
一个可以挣到外快的医生
A doctor who's got a little extra walking around money,
明白我的意思吗
if you know what I'm saying.
没门
It's not gonna happen.
我回诊断室了
I'll be in the exam room.
盖比  去拿DVD  在档案里
Gabe, get the DVD. It's in the file.
好的  嘿
Okay. Hey.
嘿  查莉  如果你去找医生玩
Hey, Charlie, if you go find the doctor,
我就给你糖吃  好吗
I'll give you some candy, okay?
-好  -好的  去吧
-Okay. -Okay, come on.
去找他
Find him.
噢   不好了
Oh, no!
我的“小咩咩”跑进诊断室了
My "wittle sisto" has run into the exam room!
她不能进去
She can't go in there.
“戴利  戴维斯”  噢  “邓肯”  拿到了  老爸  过来
"Daley, Davis." Oh, "duncan. " Got it. Dad, come on.
噢  可把你找到了  你个小淘气鬼
Oh, there you are, you little dickens.
我的糖呢
Where's my candy?
糖
Candy.
为了让你跑开吗  噢  怎么可能
For running away? Oh, I don't think so.
走吧
Come on.
我看起来怎么样
So how do I look?
惊艳  简直美若天仙
Amazing. You look incredible.
那我们还在等什么
What are we waiting for?
还不赶快进去  闪瞎群众的双眼
Let's get in there and let people see me. Huh?
噢  有短信
<i>Oh, who's texting me?</i>
噢  是PJ
Oh, it's P.J.
看吧  这是我的舞会夜
Well, here's my prom night.
发现泰勒是在家上学的
<i>Turns out taylor</i> <i>is homeschooled.</i>
本应该是我人生中最美妙的一晚
So what was supposed to be the greatest night of my life
如今剩下的只是怪异
is now the strangest.
但是我不应该抱怨
But I guess I shouldn't complain.
我被选为了舞会国王
I was voted prom King.
可怜的PJ
Poor P.J.
这是他的毕业舞会  而且悲剧了
It's his senior prom and he's miserable.
是啊  可惜了
Yeah, that's a shame.
好了  走吧
Okay, let's go in.
卡普医生  你看见邓肯的DVD了吗
Dr. Karp, have you seen the Duncan DVD?
-我找不到了  -艾米·邓肯吗
-I can't find it. -Amy Duncan?
不是  是安吉拉·邓肯
No, Angela Duncan.
怀三胞胎的那个
The one who's having triplets.
噢  天啊  我永远也别想有自己的房间了
Awww, man, I'm never getting my own room.
嘿  注意了  大家
Hey, look out, everyone.
这个舞会真是火爆了
This prom's officially been crashed!
-耶  好耶  -耶  嗯哼
-Yeah, all right! -Yeah, uh-huh!
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
收到了你的短信
We got your text
而且你的舞会看起来这么奇葩
and your prom looked so unique...
-是的  -于是我们就来了
-Right. -That we just had to come.
是啊  远离那帮吵闹的人们也不错
Yeah, what a relief to be away from all those noisy people,
笑声啊  娱乐啊
laughing and having fun.
这里好多了
This is so much better.
泰迪  你为了我放弃了自己的舞会吗
Teddy, you gave up your prom for me?
噢  别这么说
Oh, please.
去正常学校的舞会太过时了
Going to prom at regular school is so last year.
谢谢
Thank you.
在吗  PJ  是这里吗
<i>Hello, P.J.,</i> <i>are we in the right place?</i>
老妈来干什么
What's mom doing here?
你群发的短信吗
Did you send that text to everybody?
是啊  纯属意外
Yeah, it was an accident.
老奶奶和我跳舞的时候总是乱摸
Grandma was getting kinda handsy during the slow dance.
不能让她看见我穿这条裙子  还有别的出口吗
She can't see me in this dress. Is there another way out of here?
-后面有扇门  -好的  我去换衣服了
-There's a door around the back. -Okay, I'm gonna go change.
-给我掩护  -等等
-Cover for me. -Wait...
-嗨  大家好  -嘿  嘿
-hi, everyone. -Hey, hey!
老爸  老妈  你们怎么来了
Mom, dad, what are you guys doing here?
这个嘛  虽然我们无法参加自己的舞会
Well, we couldn't go to our prom,
于是我们就想  为什么不参加你们的呢
so we thought, why not go to yours?
噢  你们真好
Aww, you guys are the best.
-嘿  好啊  -嘿  斯宾塞
-Hey, there. -Hey, Spencer,
-你怎么也在这里  泰迪呢  -不知道啊
-what are you doing here? Where's Teddy? -I don't know.
她会马上回来的  三分钟吧
She'll be back in, like, three minutes.
-是啊  说到三  亲爱的  我们需要谈谈了  -我回来了
-Yeah, speaking of three, honey, we really need to talk. -<i>I'm back!</i>
我来了  嗨
I'm back. Hi.
为什么把裙子反着穿
Why is your dress on backwards?
好吧  我招了  老妈  事情是这样的
Okay, all right, mom, the truth is
之所以我不喜欢穿这条裙子
the reason why I didn't wanna wear this dress
是因为  我不喜欢
is because I... I just don't like it.
有啥不喜欢的呢
What's not to like?
穿在我身上
On... on me.
你看  问题就是
See, the problem with such
如此漂亮的一条裙子
a beautiful dress
只有你才能穿出它的美
is that it only works on you.
老妈  没人能比你穿得更好看了
No one can do justice to this dress like you, mom.
泰迪  泰迪  泰迪  泰迪
Teddy, Teddy, Teddy, Teddy.
宝贝  如果你是在建议
Honey, if you are suggesting
让我穿上这套礼服和戴上这顶帽子
that I put that dress and this hat on
因为此时此刻我们在一个舞会上
because we are at a prom at this very moment,
那好  我将斩钉截铁的答应你
well, the answer would be a resounding okay.
那我们去换衣服吧
Let's go change.
好的
Okay.
你不介意参加这个舞会吗
You don't mind being here?
只要能和你在一起  天涯海角都可以
As long as I'm with you, I don't care where we are.
噢  嘿  坐下歇会  奶奶
Awww. Hey, take a seat, grandma.
没戏的
It's not gonna happen.
我希望能再见到你
I Hope I get to see you again,
但不知道还有机会吗  我马上要去大学了
but I don't know, I'm off to college soon.
-哪所大学  -娱乐室
-Where you going? -The rec room.
亲爱的  这可能不是你想在舞会上听到的
Honey, this probably isn't what you were expecting
但是你还记得那个超声波吗
to hear at your prom, but you remember the ultrasound
-我们决定不去看的  -记得
-we decided not to look at? -Yes.
-我看了  -什么  噢  老鲍啊
-I looked. -What?! Oh, Bob.
别告诉我  好吗  我不想知道结果
Don't tell me, okay? I don't want to know what we're having.
-那至少我能告诉你是几胞胎吗  -什么
-Well, can I at least tell you how many we're having? -What?
亲爱的  是三胞胎
Honey, we're having triplets.
噢  别逗了  那为什么医生不告诉我
Oh, come on, why wouldn't the doctor tell me?
我不知道  反正我是亲眼所见
I don't know, but I saw them.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
你是说
You mean...
一共有七个孩子
Seven kids.
哇
Wow.
我感觉我要呕了
I think I'm gonna hurl.
哇  看呐  和上次吐的位置一模一样
Wow! Look at that. She hit the exact same spot.
好了  亲
Okay, honey,
我来给你找位护士吧
let's get you to the nurse.
好了  查莉  人言道  你永远都无法忘记自己的舞会
Well, charlie, they say you never forget your prom,
我准备挑战下
but I'm gonna try real hard.
PJ  你穿这么整齐去哪啊
P.J., where you going all dressed up?
泰勒毕业了  马上回来  二十分钟
Taylor's graduation. Back in, like, 20.
最终得知  好消息  老妈怀的不是三胞胎
Turns out, good news, mom's not really having triplets.
噢  我把老妈的裙子送到了
Oh, and I took mom's prom dress
干洗店  毁尸灭迹了
to the dry cleaners, where it got destroyed.
多收了我十块钱  你以后会感激我的
Cost me 10 bucks extra. You'll thank me for it later.
你刚才说什么呢
What did you just say?
祝我好运吧  查莉
Wish me good luck, Charlie.
嘿  卡普医生
Hey, Dr. Karp,
我奶奶有个很重要的问题想问你
well, my grandmother has a very important question to ask you.
-嘿  奶奶  -你好啊
-Hey, grandma. -Well, hello!
你是邓肯老奶奶吗
You're grandma Duncan?
噢  直接叫我格拉迪斯吧
Oh, why don't you just call me Gladys?
那个谁  我迫切的想知道
Anywho, I am dying to know
我马上迎来的是
if my new grandchild
孙子啊  还是孙女啊
is a boy or a girl.
对你我也有同样的疑问
I was wondering the same thing about you.
卡普医生
Dr. Karp.
-妈  -噢  好啊  儿子
-Mom? -Oh hello, son.
这么说  她真的是你
So... she's really is your...
是啊  怪吧
Yeah, pretty freaky, isn't it?
好了  医生  快说吧
Well, doctor, out with it.
好吧  好吧  我告诉你们
All right, all right, I'll tell you.
新生儿将是
The new baby is going to be a...